let questionsData = [
    {
        "question" : "Who is the former manager of Dunder Mifflin Stamford?",
        "a"        : "Josh Porter",
        "b"        : "Jan Levinson",
        "c"        : "Charles Miner",
        "d"        : "Deangelo Vickers",
        "correct"  : "a"
    },

    {
        "question" : "What kind of bear is best?",
        "a"        : "Polar Bear",
        "b"        : "Grizzly Bear",
        "c"        : "Kodiak Bear",
        "d"        : "Black Bear",
        "correct"  : "d"
    },

    {
        "question" : "In S1E2 \"Diversity Day\": What famous comedian's stand up routine does Michael imitate?",
        "a"        : "Chris Rock",
        "b"        : "Richard Pryor",
        "c"        : "Robin Williams",
        "d"        : "George Carlin",
        "correct"  : "a"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Why does Pam refuse to attend sporting events with Roy?",
        "a"        : "She once was struck in the neck by a foul ball",
        "b"        : "Roy once left her at a hockey game",
        "c"        : "Roy insists on painting his face",
        "d"        : "When Roy's teams lose, he drives like a crazy person",
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Michael attended high school with one of his employees. Which one?",
        "a"        : "Oscar Martinez",
        "b"        : "Toby Flenderson",
        "c"        : "Phyllis (Lapin) Vance",
        "d"        : "Stanley Hudson",
        "correct"  : "c"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Complete this Michael Scott quote: \"You know what they say in the Bible about forgiveness. ________________.\"",
        "a"        : '"Jesus was all about it."',
        "b"        : '"Forgiveness is next to Godliness."',
        "c"        : "\"Forgive or we'll see you in hell.\"",
        "d"        : '"Just do it."',
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Where did Andy Bernard attend college?",
        "a"        : "Cornell",
        "b"        : "Dartmouth",
        "c"        : "Syracuse",
        "d"        : "Harvard",
        "correct"  : "a"
    },

    {
        "question" : "After the Fun Run to beat Rabies, to whom is the oversized check made out?",
        "a"        : "Rabies",
        "b"        : "Meredith",
        "c"        : "Michael Scott",
        "d"        : "Science",
        "correct"  : "d"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following cast members is NOT one of the show's writers?",
        "a"        : "B.J. Novak (\"Ryan Howard\")",
        "b"        : "Phyllis Smith (\"Phyllis (Lapin) Vance\")",
        "c"        : "Paul Lieberstein (\"Toby Flenderson\")",
        "d"        : "Mindy Kaling (\"Kelly Kapoor\")",
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following costumes has Michael NOT worn for Halloween?",
        "a"        : "Adolf Hitler",
        "b"        : "Monica Lewinsky",
        "c"        : "Janet Jackson's Boob",
        "d"        : "O.J. Simpson",
        "correct"  : "a"
    },

    {
        "question" : "In S1E3 \"Health Care\": Which of these is NOT one of Jim and Pam's made up diseases?",
        "a"        : "Killer Nanorobots",
        "b"        : "Hot dog fingers",
        "c"        : "Spontaneous dental hydroplosion",
        "d"        : "Hair cancer",
        "correct"  : "d"
    },

    {
        "question" : "In one of Michael's confusing analogies, he is both Chandler and Joey. Pam is Rachel. Who is Dwight?",
        "a"        : "Gunther",
        "b"        : "Mr. Furley",
        "c"        : "Kramer",
        "d"        : "Cliff Clavin",
        "correct"  : "c"
    },

    {
        "question" : "What's the name of Michael's screenplay, which Pam finds in his drawer?",
        "a"        : "Agent Michael Scarn",
        "b"        : "Prognosis Negative",
        "c"        : "Firestorm",
        "d"        : "Threat Level: Midnight",
        "correct"  : "d"
    },

    {
        "question" : "At the company picnic, which branch received news of closing?",
        "a"        : "Albany",
        "b"        : "Buffalo",
        "c"        : "Akron",
        "d"        : "Rochester",
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "When Dwight lies and tells everyone they are getting a thousand dollar raise, what does Stanley tell his wife to buy?",
        "a"        : "A car",
        "b"        : "New Shoes",
        "c"        : "A new TV",
        "d"        : "Wallpaper",
        "correct"  : "d"
    },

    {
        "question" : "What is the password to Michael's computer?",
        "a"        : "1111",
        "b"        : "0123",
        "c"        : "1234",
        "d"        : "4519",
        "correct"  : "c"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Dwight Claims to raise his _____ at will.",
        "a"        : "Paycheck",
        "b"        : "Body temperature",
        "c"        : "Cholesterol",
        "d"        : "None of the above",
        "correct"  : "c"
    },
        
    {
        "question" : "In S1E1 \"Pilot\": Who started their first day at Dunder Mifflin Scranton?",
        "a"        : "Jim Halpert",
        "b"        : "Ryan Howard",
        "c"        : "Michael Scott",
        "d"        : "Erin Hannon",
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "What was Michael cooking on his George Foreman grill when he got burnt?",
        "a"        : "Steak",
        "b"        : "Bacon",
        "c"        : "Hamburgers",
        "d"        : "Chicken",
        "correct"  : "b"
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which is NOT a game that Kevin and Oscar play at their desks?",
        "a"        : "Hate Ball",
        "b"        : "Who can put the most M&Ms in Their Mouth?",
        "c"        : "Flonkerton",
        "d"        : "Dunderball",
        "correct"  : "c"
    },
]